AMAZlNG DlSCOVERlES
伟大的发明
Welcome,everybody! Welcome to Amazing Discoveries!
欢迎各位收看 “伟大的发明”！
It's on again!
又播出了！
Guys,could we please not watch this?
我们能不能别看了啊？
This ever happen to you? You go to get a glass of milk...
你是否遇过这种情形？ 你正打算倒一杯牛奶…
...but these cartons are so flinging,flanging hard to open!
但你左思右想 却怎么也打不开纸盒
Boy,you said it,Mike.
天啊，你说对了，麦克
- There's gotta be a better way. - There is,Kevin!
一定有个好办法 的确有，凯文
-Can we please turn this off? -No way,Kevin!
可不可以别看了？ 不行，凯文
What if I told you there's a new product that guarantees...
如果我告诉你有个新产品 能保证…
... you'll never have to open up milk cartons again?
你再也不用费力 打开牛奶纸盒呢？
Meet the Milkmaster 2000!
看看2000年的牛奶大师！
-lntrigued? -You're flinging,flanging right I am!
挑起你的兴趣了吧 是啊，挑得我心痒痒的
This is the first time he's used this. You'll see how easy this is to do.
这是他第一次使用 你就知道有多容易了
-This works in any milk carton. -Wow,it is easy!
任何牛奶纸盒都适用 真简单！
Now I can have milk every day.
这样我就可以每天喝牛奶了
The One With the Metaphorical Tunnel
本集播出： “迈向另一端的承诺”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
It's official. There are no good movies.
真的没有好看的电影
So let's go to a bad one, and make out.
那就去看难看的电影 然后在那里亲热
Perhaps you'd like me to turn so you can bunny-bump against my back?
或许你希望我转过去 你们就可以靠着我的背玩？
-Hey,man. What's up? -Maybe you can tell me.
老兄，怎么了？ 或许该由你来告诉我吧
My agent wants to know why I didn't show up at my audition today...
我的经纪人问我 为何今天的试演没有出席
... my first good one in weeks. How could you not give me the message?
这几周来第一个好机会 你怎么没转告我？
I'll tell you,I do enjoy guilt...
告诉你，我虽然喜欢罪恶感…
... but it wasn't me.
但这次不是我
Yes,it was. It was him!
是的，就是他！
Okay,it was me!
好吧，是我啦
-How was it you? -Well,it was all so crazy,you know?
怎么会是你？ 一切真是疯狂啊，你知道吗？
Chandler was in the closet, counting to 10...
钱德躲在衣橱里，倒数十秒…
...and I hadn't found a place to hide yet.
已经数到七了 我一直找不到地方躲
I meant to tell you,and I wrote it all down on my hand. See? All of it.
我一直想告诉你，我写在手上 你看，全都在这儿
Yep,that's my audition.
是啊，就是我的试镜
See? Now,this is why I keep notepads everywhere.
看吧，这就是为何 我到处都要放便条纸
Yep. And that's why we don't invite you to play.
对，这就是为何 我们都不邀你一起玩
What is the great tragedy here? Get yourself another appointment.
这样有什么可怜的？ 再约一次时间啊
Estelle tried. The casting director told her I missed my chance.
艾斯特试过了，选角导演说 我已经错过了机会
Well,that is unfair!
这样太不公平了！
I'll call her. I'll tell her it was my fault.
我来打给她 我告诉她都是我的错
You can't. The casting director doesn't talk to friends.
不，选角导演不可能 跟演员的朋友谈
-She only talks to agents. -What a sad little life she must lead.
她只跟经纪人谈 她的生活层面真狭隘啊
-What are you doing? -No,I know,I know.
你在干嘛？ 我知道啦…
Hi,this is Caitlin from Phoebe Buffay's office.
我是菲比布菲公司的凯特琳
Is Anne there for Phoebe?
菲比可以和安谈一谈吗？
She'll know what it's about.
她自己明白是什么事
Hang up. Hang up right
挂掉，快挂掉…
Annie? Hi. Listen,we've got a problem with Joey Tribbiani.
安妮，你好 乔伊崔比亚尼有点小问题
Apparently,he missed his audition. Who did you speak to in my office?
很显然地，他错过了试演 你是转告我们公司的哪一位？
Estelle? I don't know what to do with her.
艾斯特？ 我真不知该拿她怎么办
So your husband leaves and burns down the apartment. The world doesn't stop.
就算丈夫离开，并放火烧房子 世界依旧照常运作
Is anybody else scared?
还有其他人受到惊吓吗？
If Joey loses this audition,then that is it for Estelle. I don't care!
若乔伊错失这次试演 那是艾斯特的错，我不管！
Annie,you are a doll. What time can you see him? I need a pen. Pen!
安妮，你真善良 你何时能见他？我需要笔！
Get the woman a pad! Get the woman a pad! A pad! A pad!
快给这个女人一本便条纸 给她便条纸，快点！
Oh,now you want a pad.
现在你就需要便条纸啦
Where's my boy?
我的小男孩呢？
Here's my boy!
我的小男孩在这儿
And here's his Barbie!
还有他的芭比娃娃！
What's my boy doing with a Barbie?
我儿子干嘛玩芭比娃娃？
He picked it out at the store. He loves it.
他自己在玩具店选的 他很喜欢呢
He carries it everywhere, like a security blanket.
他去哪儿都带着它 就像能给他安全感的小毯子
But with ski boots and a kicky beret.
这个却穿着雪靴 和时髦的法国帽
Yeah,it's cute.
是啊，很可爱
Why does he have it again?
再说一次 他为何要玩这个东西？
So he's got a doll. So what?
他有个洋娃娃，那又怎样？
Unless you're afraid he's gonna grow up to be...
除非你怕他将来 长大后变成…
...in show business.
演艺圈的人
This wouldn't have to do with the fact...
这件事跟他…
...that he's being raised by two women?
被两个女人扶养长大 有没有关系？
You know what? It's fine. If you're okay with the Barbie thing,so am l.
好，若你能接受他喜欢芭比 那我也可以
Give Daddy the Barbie. Give me the Barbie.
把芭比给爸爸，芭比给我
Don't you wanna play with a monster truck?
你要不要玩怪兽车？
No? Okay.
不要？好吧
How about a Dino-Soldier?
那要不要恐龙士兵？
You are so pathetic.
罗斯，你真可悲
Why can't your son just play with his doll?
为何不让你的儿子玩芭比？
I gotta go to work.
我要去上班了
Has anybody seen my left boob?
有人看到我左边的胸部吗？
I loved that movie.
我喜欢那部电影
Here it is. What are you doing?
在这里，你在干嘛？
I'm sorry. It just felt nice.
对不起，这样很舒服
Answer the phone.
去接电话
I only got one arm. You should do stuff for me. Get me a sweater.
我只有一只手，你应该帮我的 帮我拿件毛衣来
Just do it! It's Janice.
快点接啦！是珍妮丝
And if I get it,I'll have to see her tonight.
如果我接了 我今晚就得跟她见面
That's great. I'll have to see her tonight.
那太好了 我今晚得跟她见面
Why don't you want to see Janice?
你为何不想见她？
Last night at dinner, when the meals came...
昨晚我们在吃晚餐 当餐点送来时…
...she put half her chicken piccata on my plate and took all my tomatoes.
她把一半烤鸡肉放到我盘里 拿走我所有的番茄
And that's bad...
这样很不好是因为…
...because you hate chicken piccata?
你不喜欢烤鸡肉吗？
You didn't want to share your tomatoes. Tomatoes are very important to you.
你不想与人分享你的番茄 番茄对你很重要
Suddenly,we were this "couple."
突然间，我们就是“情侣”了
And this alarm started going off in my head.
然后我脑袋里的警报开始大响
"Run for your life! Get out of the building!"
“为了你的人生，快跑！ 快离开这栋大楼！”
Men are unbelievable.
男人真是令人难以置信
What is it with you people?
你们这些人是怎么回事？
The minute you feel something, you have to run away?
心中一旦产生感情 就要马上逃开？
I know. That
我知道，那就是…
That's why I don't want to go tonight. I'm afraid I'll say something stupid.
就是我今晚不想去的原因 我怕自己说出一些蠢话
You mean that "guy thing" where you act mean and distant...
你是说男人那一套 故意冷漠，保持距离…
... until we break up with you?
直到我们跟你们分手？
You know about that?
你们都知道啊？
What do I do? I wanna get past this.
我能怎么做？ 我想度过这个阶段
I don't want to be afraid of commitment.
我不想再害怕承诺
I want to go through the tunnel to the other side!
就像跃过一个隧道 到达另一端！
Where there's no fear of commitment.
就是不再害怕承诺
Do we have any
我们有没有…
Do we have any thoughts here?
有没有任何想法？
I've never been through the tunnel myself because...
我没度过那种隧道啦 因为…
...you're not allowed through with more than one girl in the car.
过隧道的规定是 你车里不能多于一个女生
But it seems to me it's pretty much like anything else. Face your fear.
但我看来，跟其他事差不多 你得面对恐惧
Fear of heights? Go to the top of the building.
你怕高的话，就到大楼顶端
You're afraid of bugs.
你怕虫的话…
Get a bug.
就买台金龟车吧
You have a fear of commitment.
你的情况是，你害怕承诺…
So I say you go in there and you be the most committed guy there ever was!
你就到那里去 做一个最勇于承诺的男人
Amazingly,that makes sense.
令人讶异的是，很有道理呢
-Do you think? -Oh,yeah! Go for it,man!
你这么觉得？ 是啊，快去吧，老兄！
Jump off the high dive!
从高处跳下水！
Stare down the barrel of the gun! Pee into the wind!
用目光击退枪枝！ 在风中撒尿！
If I'm staring down the barrel of a gun...
若我得用目光击退枪枝…
...I'm gonna be pretty much peeing every which way.
我大概已经尿得到处都是了
CENTRAL PERK
“中央公园”
It's your audition from this morning!
是你今天早上的试演！
Can I use the phone?
可以借用你的电话吗？
Sure,that's what it's there for. Emergencies and pretend agents.
当然，这是紧急事件 以及冒牌经纪人专用
Come on,baby! Come on!
快啊，宝贝
Hi. I have Phoebe Buffay returning a page.
菲比布菲要回覆呼叫
Okay,she's in her car. I'll have to patch you through.
好，她在车上 我帮你接过去
Very nice touch.
演得很好
Okay,go ahead.
好，继续啊
Talk,talk,talk!
快说话…
Hi,Annie?
安妮，你好
Fantastic. You got it!
太好了，你成功了！
Will he work for scale,you ask me? Well,I don't know about that.
你问我他是否要最低工资 我也不知道
Except that I do and he will.
除非我知道，而且他也愿意
Great. Oh,you are such a sweetheart.
太好了，你人真好
I would love to have lunch with you!
我很愿意与你共进午餐！
How about we have lunch next
不如就下个…
Went through a tunnel.
正经过隧道
Unbelievable.
难以置信
Oh,thank you so much!
太感谢你了
It was really fun. I mean,I've never talked on a car phone before.
真有趣，我从未用过汽车电话
You are so amazing! Could you do me this huge favor?
你真了不起 你能不能帮我个大忙？
There's another audition I want, and Estelle couldn't get me in.
还有一个试演，我很想参加 但艾斯特无法帮我搞定
I don't know. It was fun one time,but
我不知道，一次还很好玩…
Please? It would just be this one more.
拜托，再一次就好了
Well,actually it's two.
其实是两次啦
Two?
两次？
Well,really it's three.
好啦，其实是三次
Please? You're so good at it. I love you.
拜托，你这么厉害 我爱你
Okay. But just these three,right?
好，就这三次了，好吗？
No,it's four.
不，是四次
So how come you wanted to eat in tonight?
你今天怎么会想在家吃？
Because I wanted...
因为我想…
...to give you this.
送你这个东西
Are you a puppy!
你真是可爱呢
Contact paper!
防尘纸！
What do you say when someone you're sleeping with...
一个跟你上床的人…
...gives you contact paper?
送你防尘纸，该说什么？
Wait,there's more. See,the contact paper is to go...
还有呢，你看跟它搭配的…
...in your brand new drawer!
就是你的新抽屉！
See,the drawer actually goes in my dresser.
看，其实这个抽屉 正好与我的梳妆台搭配
You didn't have to do this.
你不用这么做啊
Yes,I did.
对，我要这么做
Yes,I did. Because you're my girlfriend...
是的，我要这么做 因为你是我的女朋友
...and that's what girlfriends should get.
而女朋友就该得到这些
Well,I gotta buy a vowel...
我得求救兵了…
... because,oh,my God!
因为…我的天啊
Who would've thought that someday...
谁会想的到，有一天…
... Chandler Bing would buy me a drawer?
钱德宾会买个抽屉给我？
Well,not me.
我可想不到
But that's what's happened. And there's more.
但事实就是这样 而且还不只如此
We should take a trip.
我们应该去旅行
We should?
我们该这么做？
We're a couple, and that's what couples do.
我们是情侣，情侣就该这样
And I wanna meet your parents.
我还要去见你爸妈
We should take a trip with your parents!
我们应该跟你爸妈一起去旅行
I don't think we need to because you're tripping me out right now!
我想不用了 因为你已快把我搞迷糊了
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
No,I am.
我很好
I actually am! This is amazing.
我真的很好 真是太不可思议了
My entire life,I have feared this place.
我一生都在害怕这个时刻
And now that I'm here,it's like, what was the big deal?
但现在时候到了 我却觉得没什么大不了
I could probably say,"Let's move in together," and I'd be okay.
我可能会说“我们同居吧” 却还是若无其事
You probably want us to move in together?
你可能想跟我一起住？
-lt doesn't scare me! -Yeah,well it scares me!
我竟不会因此而害怕 是啊，但我会害怕！
I'm not even divorced yet! You just invited me over here for pasta...
我根本还没离婚！ 你只是邀我来吃意大利面…
...and now you're talking about moving in together.
而现在你就在说 要住在一起的事…
And I wasn't even that hungry.
我其实还不太饿
You know what? It's getting really late,and I should just
你知道吗？时间有点晚了 我最好先…
Don't go! I've scared you! I've said too much!
别走，我吓着你了！ 我说太多了！
I'm hopeless and awkward and desperate for love!
对于爱情，我是无药可救 笨拙却又充满渴望
Hey,Janice,it's me.
珍妮丝，是我
I wanted to apologize in advance for having chased you down the street.
我只是想在到街上追你前 先跟你道歉
Here you go,honey. This will help.
拿去吧，甜心 应该有帮助的
So I catch up to her and she says...
我追上她，然后她说…
...this relationship's going too fast and we have to slow down.
这段感情发展太快 我们得放慢脚步
That is never good.
这样绝不是好现象
Then I got all...
于是我就变得…
... needy and clingy.
很空虚又很黏人
Wait a minute. Maybe it's not so bad. How did you leave it?
等等，或许不算太糟 你们怎么结束的？
She said she'd call me.
她说她会再打给我
Oh,God.
天啊
Welcome to our side of the tunnel.
恭喜你到我们这一国来
This ice cream tastes like crap, by the way.
对了，这个冰淇淋味道好烂
Well,it's that low-cal-nondairy-soymilk junk.
因为这是低卡无乳脂 豆浆制的假冰淇淋
We save the real stuff for the truly terminal cases.
我们把真正的留到 实在无法挽留了才吃
When you're getting screwed over all the time,you gotta switch to low fat.
若你一直被搞得一团糟 你就要换成低脂的
Yeah,you do.
没错，你得这么做
You don't think I'm terminal?
你不认为我已无法挽留了？
Not at all. You're not terminal. We just need some damage control.
不尽然，你并非无法挽留 我们只要防止事情恶化
Okay. Should I call her?
好，我该打电话给她吗？
It's a critical time. If you feel yourself reaching for that phone...
这段时间很重要，一旦你发现 自己的手又伸向电话…
...go shopping,get your butt in a bubble bath.
你就去买鞋子 不然就洗个泡泡浴
If you want her back, you have got to start acting aloof.
若你希望她回来 你就得开始表现冷漠
She has to know you're not needy.
她必须知道 你不是那么需要她
So what you have to do is...
所以你要做的就是…
...you have to accidentally run into her on purpose...
假装不经意地碰到她…
...and then act aloof.
然后表现得很冷漠
So I'm not gonna lose her?
这样我就不会失去她了？
Oh,honey,you're not a total loser.
甜心，你不是个弱者啊
I said,"So I'm not gonna lose her?"
我是说 “我就不会失去她了？”
Guess who's here!
看看谁来了！
It's the toughest guy in Toyland,Ben!
是玩具王国里 最勇敢的人，班！
Real American hero I'm G.I. Joe!
真正的美国英雄 我是美国大兵！
Drop the Barbie. Drop the Barbie.
把芭比娃娃放下…
G.I. Joe?
美国大兵？
You really think he'll fall for that?
你真的觉得他会 喜欢那玩意儿？
G.I. Joe?
美国大兵？
Cool! Can I play?
好棒，我可以玩吗？
Look,Ben! It's a toy that protects U.S. oil interests overseas!
班，你看，这个玩具 保护了美国海外油股！
Go,Joe!
加油，大兵！
-There you are! -No,it's not. Sorry.
菲比，你在这儿啊 不，我不是，抱歉
But,Phoebe,wait,wait. Phoebe!
菲比，等等…
Oh,Joey! Oh,okay! See,I didn't recognize you...
乔伊啊，我刚没认出你来…
...in those pants.
因为你穿着这条裤子
That TV movie I went in for, did you hear anything?
我参加试演的小型电影 有任何回音吗？
I think I got a shot at it.
我想我应该很有机会的
Yes,they called! You didn't get it!
对，他们打来了 你没有入选
Okay? I mean,you didn't get it. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
可以吗？我是说你落选了 对不起…
That's okay. These things happen.
没关系 这种事本来就会发生
But they shouldn't happen. You know what?
但是不应该发生，你知道吗？
You're in a terrible, terrible business.
你进的这一行 真的好可怕
I don't want to be the person who makes you look like that.
我不想成为 那个让你难过的人
I'm okay. See?
我没事的，你看
Now you're sad and creepy.
你看起来很难过 让人很害怕
I'm sorry. I quit.
我很抱歉，我要辞职
No,no,you can't quit! You're the best agent I ever had.
不，你不能辞职！ 你是我遇过最好的经纪人
Rejection is part of being an actor. You can't take it personal.
当一个演员本来就会被拒绝 你不能过于自责
They said they'd never met an ltalian actor with a worse ltalian accent.
他们说没遇过一个意大利演员 有这么怪的意大利腔
They actually said that?
他们真的这么说？
Oh,God,there's that face again. See? I can't do this job!
天啊，又是那种表情 你看，我不能做这个工作
This is why you have to do this job!
这就是为何你得做这份工作
Agents always lie.
经纪人都得说谎
Estelle just says stuff like, "They went another way."
艾斯特总是说 “他们要另一种方式”
But this? I can use this.
但是这一点嘛，我可以改进
I can work on a new accent.
我可以学一种新的腔调
Yeah,okay. If it helps you,okay. Yeah.
好，若对你有帮助，那就好了
You'll never get me,Joe!
你抓不到我，士兵！
No,thank you.
不用了，谢谢
What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么？
Just a bit of shopping.
只是买买东西而已
How have you been?
你还好吗？
Are you being British?
你在装英国腔吗？
Not anymore.
再也不会了
Why are you shopping here? You don't live in this neighborhood.
你怎么在这里买东西？ 你又不住在这一带
Were you here waiting for me?
你是不是在这里等我？
I'm just...
我只是…
... picking up some things for a party.
要买一点派对用的东西
Barley?
大麦？
What kind of party serves barley?
什么样的派对会供应大麦？
I'm sorry if my friends aren't as sophisticated as yours.
很抱歉，我的朋友 不像你朋友那么有水准
Where is this party?
派对在哪里举行？
Here in Chelsea.
就在雀儿喜
Whose party is it?
是谁办的派对
A woman's.
一个女人
What woman?
哪个女人？
Chelsea.
雀儿喜
Either you're seeing somebody behind my back...
你要不是背着我跟别人约会…
...which would make you the world's biggest jerk...
然后成了世界第一混蛋…
...or you're pretending to see somebody...
不然就是你假装跟别人约会…
...which makes you so pathetic I could cry right here!
让你成为最可悲的人 我会立刻在此为你哭泣
So which of these two guys do you want to be?
这两种男人，你想当哪一种？
Can I be that guy?
我可以当那个人吗？
Okay,we got some more good rejections. Lots of stuff to work on.
我们收到很多善意的拒绝 有很多地方要改进
Okay. Shoot.
好，说吧
Okay. Oh,the zoo commercial.
好，那个动物园广告
I didn't get it?
我没得到那个角色？
They said that you "weren't believable as a human being."
他们说你简直不像个人类
So you can work on that.
所以你可以针对这一点改进
Great.
很好
What else?
还有呢？
The off-Broadway-play people said that you were "pretty but dumb."
那些小剧场的人 说你很好看，可是很笨
Oh,no wait. I'm sorry. That's "pretty dumb."
等等，对不起 他们是说你非常笨
Look,it's okay,no,no,no. Really.
看，没关系啊 不…是真的
Look...
听着…
... I really appreciate this...
我很感谢你…
... but I'm gonna have to go back to Estelle.
但我还是回去找艾斯特好了
Don't get me wrong. You're a better agent than she is...
别误会 你当经纪人当得比她好…
... but at least with her,I don't want to blow my pretty dumb brains out.
至少我跟着她 我这非常笨的脑袋还保得住
Yeah,no,I understand.
是的，不，我能了解
You do? Thanks. Okay.
你可以吗？谢谢你
Sorry.
抱歉
Wait a minute.
等一下
Did you make all that stuff up to get out of being my agent?
你是不是故意编这些出来 就不用当我的经纪人了？
Oh,he caught me.
被你发现了
I am so busted!
我完蛋了！
That's what I suspected!
我早就这么怀疑了
And then I just,you know...
然后我只好…
...threw the bag of barley at her and ran out of the store.
把一袋大麦丢到她身上 然后逃出那间店
My God,Chandler,we said be "aloof," not "a doof."
天啊，我们叫你表现冷漠 不是像个笨蛋
I've actually ruined this,haven't l?
我这次真的搞砸了，对吧？
Is it time for the good ice cream now?
这次可以吃 真正的冰淇淋了吗？
Yeah,it is.
没错，可以了
You know what? Everything's gonna be okay.
你知道吗？一切都没问题的
Can you hold on for a second?
珍妮丝，你可以等一下吗？
What do I do?
好，我该怎么办？
I don't know. This is unprecedented.
我不知道，这是史无前例的
If we did what you did, a man would never call.
若我们做出像你一样的事 男人绝不会再打来了
I got it! Pretend you just woke up. That'll throw her off!
我知道了，假装你刚睡醒 这样就可以摆脱她了
-Be sleepy! -Yes! And grumpy!
睡意惺忪的样子！ 对，脾气暴躁的感觉！
What are you? Stop naming dwarfs!
你们怎么…？ 别开始数小矮人的名字
I'm so glad that you called.
我很高兴你打来
I know I've been acting really weird lately...
我知道我最近的表现很怪…
...and it's just because I'm crazy about you...
那是因为我太爱你了
...and I just got stupid and scared...
我就变得很蠢，又很害怕…
...and stupid a couple more times.
然后就变得非常笨
And I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
Really?
真的？
He's so lucky. If Janice were a guy...
他真幸运，若珍妮丝是男的…
...she'd be sleeping with somebody else by now.
她现在已经跟别人上床了
I love you too.
我也爱你
It's so unfair!
真是太不公平了！
G. I. Joe? G. I. Joe?!
美国大兵…？
I don't know what to tell you guys. That's the doll he chose.
我不知如何告诉你们 但他真的选了这个玩具
What'd you do,dip it in sugar?
你怎么做的？ 把玩具沾糖吗？
Look,G. I. Joe's in,Barbie's out.
听着，美国大兵获胜 芭比娃娃出局了
And if you guys can't deal with it, that's just your too bad.
如果你们不能接受 那你们就太糟糕了
What are you being such a weenie for? So he has a Barbie. Big deal.
你干嘛这么小家子气 他有个芭比，有什么大不了？
You used to dress up like a woman.
你以前都打扮得像女生
What?
什么？
The way you used to dress up in Mom's clothes?
你以前都穿妈的衣服啊
What are you talking about?
你在说什么啊？
The big hat,the pearls, the little pink handbag?
宽帽子、珍珠、粉红小手提包
Okay. You are totally making this up.
好，这些都是你编出来的
How can you not remember?
你怎么可能不记得？
You made us call you "Bea"?
你还要我们叫你“碧”啊
Oh,God.
天啊
I've literally never been this happy.
我真的从没这么快乐过
Wasn't there a little song?
不是还有一首歌吗？
Oh,please,God, let there be a song.
拜托，老天，来一首歌吧
There was no song. There was no song.
根本没有什么歌…
I am Bea
我是碧
-I drink tea -That's enough.
我喝茶 够了！
Won't you....
你要不要…
Won't you dance around with me?
你要不要在我身旁跳舞？
I am Bea
我是碧
I drink tea
我喝茶
Won't you dance around with?
你要不要在我身旁跳舞…
Ross?
罗斯？